Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Objects and Artifacts, 1914-1992
  - Subseries A: General Objects and Artifacts
    - Toy spider, undated; cuid28153 (Box 180, Object 092.2.0450)
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 2.75 x 3.5 inches
    - Light set--Lizards, circa 1988; cuid28154 (Box 184, Object 092.2.0451)
      Description: "Bunch-a-Lizards" light set--contains 10 plastic gray and red lizards which fit onto a string of decorative lights.
      Maker: "Prinal Lite" printed on front and sides of box and "Sue Scott" printed lower right corner
      Where Made: Sticker on bottom states "Made in Taiwan"
      Materials: plastic, electric lights
      Dimensions: 1 x 6.5 x 3 inches
    - Firework, undated; cuid28155 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0452)
      Description: Firework with butterfly wings attached. Left wing printed in Chinese, right wing printed "Spring Butterflies (Large Size) Blue, red, orange, black.
      Maker: Top center printed with "Link Triad Brand" with logo
      Where Made: Bottom center printed "Made in Kwangsi, China"
      Materials: cardboard, fireworks
      Dimensions: 3 x 5.75 x 1.25 inches
    - Fly Toy, undated; cuid28156 (Box 133, Object 092.2.0453)
      Description: Fly with suction cup at mouth to mount on window. Green, black, red.
      Materials: plastic, paint, pipe cleaners
      Dimensions: 2 x 3.5 x 7.25 inches
    - Frog Acrobat, undated; cuid28157 (Box 176, Object 092.2.0454)
      Description: Toy made of wooden sticks with cardboard frog attached by string. Pressing bottom makes the frog flip over. In original but opened package.
      Maker: Sticker on package labeled "Club Earth"
      Where Made: sticker on package labeled "Made in China"
      Materials: wood, string, cardboard
      Dimensions: 9.15 x 2.15 x 2.25 inches
    - Alligator Figurine, undated; cuid28158 (Box 164, Object 092.2.0455)
      Description: Alligator with open mouth, gray
      Maker: Mark on underside of alligator--undetermined
      Dimensions: 1.25 x 2.5 x 8.5 inches
    - Stone in box, undated; cuid28159 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0456)
      Description: "Crocodile Scute" --flat stone with holes or gouges. In box with card identifying it as "crocodile scute"
      Materials: stone; box--cardboard, cotton, paper, ink
    - Crystal, undated; cuid28160 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0457)
      Description: Piece of crystal, possibly amethyst. White and purple.
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 2 x 1 inches
    - Pin, undated; cuid28161 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0458)
      Description: Stick pin with circular image of male saint w/child--probably Joseph and baby Jesus.
      Materials: metal, image
      Dimensions: 1.65 x 0.75 x inches
    - Crystal pendant, undated; cuid28605 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0459)
    - Crystal Pendant, undated; cuid28162 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0460)
      Description: Clear tear drop shaped pendant hung on a multi-colored thread braid with clear bead at top. Red, yellow, green.
      Materials: crystal, thread.
      Dimensions: 6.5 x 0.5inches
    - Double Sided Lithograph, undated; cuid28163 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0461)
      Description: Double sided lithograph
      Maker: No signature
      Materials: lithograph
      Dimensions: 24 x 35inches
    - Original study of pint, 1990/1991; cuid28164 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0462)
      Description: Multimedia collage with swastika in a sun, the grim reaper ('democracy at work") descending upon people with voice bubbles "saying" things like "starvation" & "homophobia"
      Maker: signature on center right bottom of piece
      Materials: oil stick, collage, press type
      Dimensions: 23 x 20inches
    - Psychiatric Clinic: Court of Benjamin Sessions, June 1, 1983; cuid28165 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0463)
      Description: Paint and Ink. Red Blood-like blotch over images of people walking and standing.
      Maker: David Wojnarowicz and Kiki Smith on bottom right hand corner below title
      Materials: Ink, Paint
      Dimensions: 17.5 x 22.5inches
    - Stencil, undated; cuid28166 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0464)
      Description: Stencil of Flames
    - Text Poster, 1985; cuid28167 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0465)
      Description: Poster--Black & White photo of man on left, text on right with red square image of 2 figures beating a third figure on the ground
      Maker: No signature, but printed on right hand side and between C & D printed along right hand side (cont)
      Materials: printed poster
      Dimensions: 16 x 22inches
    - Romulus and Remus Screen-print, 1983; cuid28168 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0466)
      Description: Screenprint--2 pieces of paper. Wolf with earth on back. Two babies suckling and the burning house stencil in his middle
      Maker: signed. Bottom left hand of image
      Materials: stencil
      Dimensions: 23 x 3inches
    - Kondoleon Poster, signed with date 1989; cuid28169 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0467)
      Description: Poster for theater for the New City. Images of Grim Reaper, train emerging from brain, and 2 figures with gun
      Maker: signed bottom center
      Materials: collage, water color paint, ink
    - Hunger, 1981; cuid28170 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0468)
      Description: Stencil print "Southern /Jumbo / Yams..." Green stencil, silver stencil of knife, plate, fork on top of green. Soldier, syringe.
      Maker: bottom left hand side, and (?) on right hand side
      Materials: stencil, spray-paint
      Dimensions: 22 x 34inches
    - Early Stencil 1, undated; cuid28171 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0469)
      Description: Stencil of gorilla with arms tied to posts.
      Maker: no signature
      Dimensions: 21 x 22inches
    - Early Band Poster 2, 1980-81; cuid28172 (Item 092.2.0247, Folder 092.2.0470)
      Description: silkscreen, "3 Teens Kill 4" Pyramid Ave A 6 & 7th st. Thurs Jan 21. In blue below green soldier running over red brick
      Maker: lower right corner
      Materials: spray-paint stencil 17.5
      Dimensions: 14 x 0inches
    - Panda Stuffed Animal, Undated; 092.2.0471; 1 item one stuffed animal (Box 092.2.0471)
      Description: Panda stuffed animal
      Maker: n/a
      Where Made: n/a
      Materials: fabric, stuffing
      Dimensions: 22 x 15.5 x 9.5 inches
      soft toys
    - Plastic clown head, undated; 092.2.0472; 1 item one toy (Box 092.2.0472)
      Description: plastic clown head, blue hat, grinning mouth, red nose, yellow and red polka dot tie.
      Dimensions: 17 x 10 x 11 inches
      Toys.
    - Clown Toy, Undated; cuid28173; 1 item one toy (Box 160, Object 092.2.0473)
      Description: Push button swinging clown toy
      Materials: plastic and paint
      Dimensions: 5.5 x 3 x 1.5 inches
    - Bull Skull, undated; 092.2.0474; 1 item one skull (Item 092.2.0474)
      Description: Bull Skull
      Materials: cow skull
      Dimensions: 5 x 17 x 11 inches
      skulls (skeleton components)
    - Skull rock and chain, undated; 092.2.0475; 1 item one rock with chain attached (Box 141, Object 092.2.0475)
      Description: round piece of rock (cement?) in shape of skull attached to a metal chain.
      Materials: rock, metal
      Dimensions: 9 x 38 x 12 inches
    - Beer keg, undated; 092.2.0476; 1 item one can (Box 145, Object 092.2.0476)
      Description: Mini beer keg. "Lowenbrau Zurich" has round holes and collapsed, rusty top and bottom
      Materials: tin
      Dimensions: 9.5 x 7 x 7 inches
      Cans (containers)
    - Large bull skull, undated; 092.2.0477; 1 item one skull with hanging fixtures on horns and lower jaw (Box 092.2.0477)
      Description: Large bull skull with hanging fixtures on horns and lower jaw
      Materials: skull, bone
      Dimensions: 16 x 20 x 20 inches
    - Wooden block, undated; cuid28174 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0478)
      Description: Toy wooden block with the letter P on one side. Image of a plane on another. The Letter H and image of a bird
      Dimensions: 1.75 x 1.75 x 1.75 inches
    - Watch, undated; cuid28175 (Box 151, Object 092.2.0479)
      Description: wrist watch with yellow face
      Maker: Swatch
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 1.25 x 4 inches
    - Beaded Band, undated; cuid28176 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0480)
      Description: Beaded band with white, blue, orange, purple, gold and green beads
      Materials: beads, string
      Dimensions: 1 x 17 inches
    - Flying beetle necklace in green box, undated; cuid28177 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0481)
      Description: Silver necklace. Scarab beetle with wings, 2 green stones and 2 white beads and chain
      Materials: silver, beads
      Dimensions: 12 x 1.5 inches
    - Oil drill coin purse, undated; cuid28178 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0482)
      Description: coin purse with side zipper and image of oil drill
      Maker: c. MAFCO on bottom left (which zips to left hand side)
      Materials: cloth, ink
      Dimensions: 4 x 3 inches
    - Bag of pink marbles, undated; cuid28179 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0483)
      Description: Plastic fishnet bag of pearly pink marbles
      Materials: pearly pink marbles in fishnet plastic sack
      Dimensions: 6 x 3 x 3 inches
    - Fingernail clipper with camouflage top, undated; cuid28180 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0485)
      Description: Small fingernail clipper/knife/can opener with camouflage plate as top
      Materials: metal, plastic
      Dimensions: 0.5 x 2.5 x 0.5 inches
    - Yellow beads in plastic bag, undated; cuid28181 (Box 151, Object 092.2.0484)
      Description: Plastic beads in clear bag with price on outside
      Materials: yellow beads in fishing wire inside plastic bag
      Dimensions: 5.5 x 3 x 0.5 inches
    - Tin Heart Ornament, undated; cuid28182 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0486)
      Description: Tin ornament with a heart on the center, designs surrounding the heart, and sharp pointed edges. "GR" engraved in center with dots.
      Materials: Tin
      Dimensions: 3 x 2.25 inches
    - Bag of mixed color beads, undated; cuid28183 (Box 151, Object 092.2.0487)
      Description: Multi-colored beads in a plastic bag. Nylon bead card also included.
      Materials: beads (red, orange, green, white); nylon cord; plastic bag
      Dimensions: 5.34 x 3 x 25 inches
    - Stamp flag and bag of stamps, undated; cuid28184 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0488)
      Description: Waxed paper bag of loose 25 cent and one 25 cent with $ written on it, attached to blue stir stick.
      Materials: USPS stamps (25 cent), tape, stirring stick
      Dimensions: 2 x 4.25 inches
    - Dog tags on chain, 1990; cuid28185 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0489)
      Description: One dog tag reads "Oh I want to Farm that blowboy" and the other "David Wojnarowicz 1990"
      Maker: Dog tag
      Dimensions: 1.25 x 2 x 0.25 inches
    - Blue snake tail string, undated; cuid28186 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0490)
      Description: String of large blue beads and snake tail at bottom. Blue piece at top reads "poison".
      Materials: glass, rattle snake tail
      Dimensions: 5.5 x 0.5 inches
    - American Flag stitched to banner "Lionel", undated; cuid28187 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0491)
      Description: Stitched American flag sewn to string and to banner
      Materials: cloth, string
      Dimensions: 16 x 3 inches
    - Clock face, 4/17/1995; cuid28188 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0492)
      Description: Metal clock face
      Dimensions: 2 x 2 inches
    - Pipe, undated; cuid28189 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0493)
      Description: Plastic pipe, wood-look, carved sides, "medico" on side
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 5 x 1.5 inches
    - Copper Pierced Heart Ornament, undated; cuid28190 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0494)
      Description: Copper heart, engraved with patterns, pierced by arrow, string tied around top.
      Materials: copper, string
      Dimensions: 35 x 3 inches
    - Charms "B" and Gold Bead Chain, undated; cuid28191 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0495)
      Description: Assorted metal charms including skull, "Roma," and more. Gold beaded chain.
      Dimensions: 0.5 x 0.5 inches
    - 2 Ring, undated; cuid28192 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0496)
      Description: 2 rings, one gold in color, the other silver with blue
      Dimensions: 1 x 1 x 5 inches
    - Spinning globe trinket, undated; cuid28193 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0497)
      Description: metal spinning globe with ring on top. Continents marked by name.
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 1.5 x 1 inches
    - Larger Trinkets, undated; cuid28194 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0498)
      Description: "1. Green splotchy smooth stone2. Clear ball pendant with ""seed"" inside.3. Green plastic clump4.Frog pin5.""Gold"" lock"
      Materials: plastic, stone, metal
    - Clock Face, undated; cuid28195 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0499)
      Description: Metal clock face; white w/ black lettering
      Maker: -----
      Where Made: ------
    - "Oaxaca" Pin, undated; cuid28196 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0500)
      Description: Metal pin of human figure dancing & wearing a large hat. Brightly colored.
      Maker: ----
      Where Made: ----
      Dimensions: 4 x 1.5 x inches
    - Turtle Pendant, undated; cuid28197 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0501)
      Description: Marble-esque pendant "925" engraved on turtle's harness--on belly
      Maker: ---
      Where Made: ---
      Materials: marble?, metal1.5.5
    - 4 Blue Beads, undated; cuid28198 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0502)
      Description: 4 blue beads in plastic bag
      Materials: ceramic (?)
      Dimensions: 0.15 x 0.15 x 0.15 inches
    - Small stone Head, undated; cuid28199 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0503)
      Description: Green and white head with chunks missing.
      Materials: stone?
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 0.5 x 0.5 inches
    - Charms "A", undated; cuid28200 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0504)
      Description: Assorted Metal Charms
    - Fabric Stick in Glass Jar, undated; cuid28201 (Box 136, Object 092.2.0505)
      Description: Fabric covered stick in glass mason jar
      Materials: glass, fabric
      Dimensions: 9.5 x 5 x 5 inches
    - Multi-colored Beetle in Plastic Box, undated; cuid28202 (Box 183, Object 092.2.0506)
      Description: Green and orange beetle. "Eudicella Grall: Hubin." In plastic box.
      Materials: Beetle, pins, foam board, plastic box
      Dimensions: 2 x 2.5 x 3.5 inches
    - Scorpion in Green Diamond-cube, undated; cuid28203 (Box 178, Object 092.2.0507)
      Description: Green "diamond-cube" with dried (real) scorpion inside
      Materials: plastic, scorpion
      Dimensions: 3 x 7 x 7 inches
    - Red Shawl, undated; cuid28204 (Box 150, Object 092.2.0508)
      Description: Red-fabric shawl with darker red designs
      Materials: cloth
      Dimensions: 33 x 77 inches
    - Two and a half horseshoes, Undated; cuid28205; 3 items two horseshoes and one half of a horseshoe (Box 128, Object 092.2.0531)
      Description: 2 full horseshoes and a half a horseshoe
      Materials: Iron, horseshoes?
      Dimensions: 4 x 5inches
      Horseshoes (animal equipment)
    - Horseshoe magnet set, Undated; cuid28206; 1 item one package of horseshoe-shaped magnets (Box 137, Object 092.2.0532)
      Description: Packages of horseshoe magnets
      Materials: plastic, magnet, metal, paper
      Dimensions: 8 x 5.5 x 0.25 inches
      Magnets.
    - Pavement chip, Undated; cuid28207; 1 item one piece of pavement (Box 164, Object 092.2.0533)
      Description: Piece of pavement chip with black paint, round circle in white "1:12" written in pencil
      Materials: Pavement, paint, pencil
      Dimensions: 4.5 x 4.75 x 0.15 inches
      Pavements (surface elements)
    - Bag of syringes & adrenaline, Undated; cuid28208; 1 item one plastic bag with syringes and adrenaline (Box 160, Object 092.2.0534)
      Description: Plastic bag of syringes and adrenaline.
      Materials: syringes, adrenaline chloride solution
      Dimensions: 9 x 5 x 1.5 inches
    - Money House 1, undated; 092.2.0535; 1 item one box (Box 142, Object 092.2.0535)
      Description: 1 of three houses--largest--All nest together. Originally shown at P.P.O.W date unknown. Included in original inventory by MR (4/28/1995) "B-2"
      Materials: cardboard, paper
      Dimensions: 17.25 x 14 x 16.75 inches
      Props (object genres)
    - Money House 2, undated; 092.2.0536; 1 item one box (Box 142, Object 092.2.0536)
      Description: 1 pf 3 houses-medium-- All nest together. Originally shown at P.P.O.W, date unknown. Included in original inventory by MR (4/28/1995) "B-2"
      Dimensions: 12 x 11 x 12 inches
    - Money House 3, undated; MSS.092.2.0537; 1 item one box (Box 142, Object MSS.092.2.0537)
      Description: 1 of 3 houses--all nest together--originally shown at P.P.O.W., date unknown. Included in original inventory by MR (4/28/1995) "B-2"
    - Small Monkey Skull, undated; cuid28209 (Box 139, Object 092.2.0538)
      Description: Small monkey skull with "#413" written in pencil on bottom
      Materials: skull
      Dimensions: 2.5 x 2 x 4.5 inches
    - Stuffed Reptile, undated; 092.2.0541; 1 item one taxidermied reptile (Box 092.2.0541)
      Description: Bleached stuffed alligator. Front legs tied to each other with rope. Back legs tied together with rope. Visible stuff line along the bottom (belly area) and visible stuffing)
      Materials: alligator, rope, stuffing
      Dimensions: 2 x 7.5 x 35 inches
      Taxidermy mounts.
    - Cow skull, undated; 092.2.0542; 1 item one skull (Box 092.2.0542)
      Description: Cow skull found in the desert with worm casings
      Materials: cow skull, worm casings
      Dimensions: 7 x 8 x 18 inches
    - Wolf's head, Undated; cuid28210; 1 item one sculpture (Box 092.2.0603)
      Description: Papier-mache mask in shape of wolf's head. Head made of New York City newspapers with AIDS-related headlines visible. Edge of mouth, inside of ears, and edges of eye holes painted red. Teeth made of cardboard, painted white. Mouth is open, large red-painted papier-mache tongue visible.
      Materials: Materials/medium description papier mache, corrugated cardboard, masking tape, paint
      Dimensions: 26 x 19 x 14 inches
  - Subseries B: The "Magic Box"
    The Magic Box is a group of fifty-nine small objects collected by Wojnarowicz and stored by him in a pine fruit box labeled "Magic Box." According to Tom Rauffenbart, Wojnarowicz kept the box under his bed and never discussed its function or significance. The objects range from organic materials such as stones and dried flowers, to commercial products like jewelry and plastic toys.
    - Magic Box, undated; 092.2.0543 (Box 188, Item 092.2.0543, Box 092.2.0543)
      Description: Wooden box with sliding lid painted in orange and green: Indian River Citrus on top and Florida's Finest Citrus on the front and back. Strip of masking tape on top with Magic Box written in marker.
      Maker: Title Magic Box is in Wojnarowicz's handwriting.
      Materials: pine box, nails, green and orange paint, masking tape.
      Dimensions: 8 x 17 x 12.625 inches
    - Bag of Insects and Bugs, undated; 092.2.0544 (Box 117, Item 092.2.0544)
      Description: Unopened plastic bag with sixteen plastic insects and spiders. Paper label on the bag reads: 16 pcs. Insects and Bugs, Ages 13 and up. Made in China, no. 3874, Fishel. Price tag: Cliff's $2.00
      Materials: plastic, paper, cardboard.
      Dimensions: 8.5 x 6 x 1.5 inches
    - Cloth Snake, undated; 092.2.0545 (Box 116, Item 092.2.0545)
      Description: Green and white striped cloth stuff snake, with embroidered dots of green, purple, red and yellow.
      Materials: cotton, stuffing material, thread.
      Dimensions: 6.375 x 9 x 1.75 inches
    - Small Painted Mammal Skull, undated; 092.2.0546 (Box 113, Item 092.2.0546)
      Description: Blue painted skull with wire attached at the back of the head.
      Maker: Andreas Senser
      Materials: unknown material, wire, blue paint.
      Dimensions: 4 x 2.875 x 2.875 inches
    - Toy Alligator with Feather, undated; 092.2.0547 (Box 116, Item 092.2.0547)
      Description: Metal snap toy alligator (red, blue, yellow, orange and black) with brown and white feather attached at the mouth, a match.
      Materials: metal, feather, match.
    - Cross, undated; 092.2.0548 (Box 113, Item 092.2.0548)
      Description: Wooden cross with circular shell inlays (14 total), metal figure of crucified Jesus, each inlay appears to have letter (T.A.V.S.?) written in black pigment.
      Materials: wood, mother-of-pearl, bronze, metal nail, unknown pigment on shell, unknown adhesive/glue.
      Dimensions: 7.125 x 3.75 x 1 inches
    - Toy Watch, undated; 092.2.0549 (Box 117, Item 092.2.0549)
      Description: Toy watch with green felt strap, gold colored rim and red and gold face, does not work - time set at 10:30, Sat. 25. Image of flying eagle on face, backing of strap is red.
      Where Made: Japan
      Materials: felt, plastic, paper, tin.
      Dimensions: 6.5 x 1.25 x 0.1875 inches
    - Action Figure, undated; 092.2.0550 (Box 117, Item 092.2.0550)
      Description: Yellow and pink male action figure with moveable joints, brown hair.
      Materials: metal screws, plastic.
      Dimensions: 4 x 1.5 x 0.75 inches
    - Catholic Prayer Piece, undated; 092.2.0551 (Box 190, Item 092.2.0551)
      Description: Christian oval prayer peice with red plastic threaded around the border. In the center is a paper oval, on one side is the image of Christ with text: "Apostleship of Prayer, League of the Sacred Heart." Reverse side is image of a heart wrapped in thorns and cross in flames with text: "Cease, the Heart of Jesus is with me. Sacred Heart of Jesus, Thy Kingdom Come." Copyright mark: Apostleship of Prayer, 1939.
      Maker: n.d.
      Where Made: none
      Materials: plastic and paper.
      Dimensions: 2.125 x 1.75 x 0.25 inches
    - Miniature Globe, undated; 092.2.0552 (Box 155, Item 092.2.0552)
      Description: Small globe of the earth with unpainted metal rim that allows for globe to rotate.
      Materials: metal, pigment.
      Dimensions: 1.875 x 1.625 inches
    - Miniature Globe Pencil Sharpener, undated; 092.2.0553 (Box 155, Item 092.2.0553)
      Description: Small globe of earth, base functions as a pencil sharpener.
      Materials: metal and pigment.
      Dimensions: 2 x 1.5 x 1.5 inches
    - Toy Grasshopper, undated; 092.2.0554 (Box 190, Item 092.2.0554)
      Description: Green rubber toy grasshopper.
      Materials: rubber.
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 2.125 x 3.5 inches
    - Candle, undated; 092.2.0555 (Box 113, Item 092.2.0555)
      Description: Wax candle, blue base with stripes of white, red, blue, yellow and orange; surface of candle is decorated with gold stamps of flowers and leaves, cut away in a repeating pattern.
      Materials: wax, string, ribbon
      Dimensions: 4.5 x 1 x 1 inches
    - Standing Male Statuette, undated; 092.2.0556 (Box 119, Item 092.2.0556)
      Description: Wooden statue standing male figure holding a wood staff, wearing robes, holding a silver-rimmed medallion to his chest, likely a religious figure.
      Where Made: Italy
      Dimensions: 8.125 x 2.75 x 2.25 inches
    - Snowman Figurine, undated; 092.2.0557 (Box 113, Item 092.2.0557)
      Description: Figure of snowman, covered in white glitter, wearing a red and white striped scarf, a black plastic top hat, and orange carrot-shaped nose.
      Materials: plastic, flocked plastic, glitter, glue, synthetic fabric.
      Dimensions: 3.75 x 2.75 x 2.25 inches
    - Small Buddha Statue, undated; 092.2.0558 (Box 113, Item 092.2.0558)
      Description: Seated Buddha figure.
      Where Made: Mexico
      Materials: possibly ceramic
      Dimensions: 1.5 x 1.75 x 2 inches
    - Bracelet, undated; 092.2.0559 (Box 117, Item 092.2.0559)
      Description: Leather bracelet studded with silver-rimmed red stones.
      Materials: leather, metal, red plastic or ceramic
      Dimensions: 0.75 x 2.5 x 2.5 inches